Spectacular car chases, an intense hostage crisis, wild animals rampaging through
the city, and even more, will have you at the edge of your seat in...
Logorama is a animation, crime, comedy film directed by Hervé de Crécy.
Two cops portrayed by Michelin Men chase an armed Ronald McDonald
through the streets of a fictionalized, stylized city.
Ronald McDonald / Bibendum Mike / Bibendum Sheriff
(voice), played by Bob Stephenson.
Bibendum Mitch (voice), played by Sherman Augustus.
Esso Girl (voice), played by Aja Evans.
Big Boy / Green Giant / Mr. Clean (voice), played by Joel Michaely.
Haribo (voice), played by Matt Winston.
Pringles Hot & Spicy (voice), played by Andrew Kevin Walker.
Logorama is a 2009 French adult animated satirical short film produced by the French graphic
design and animation studio H5 as their first and only cinematic project.
Co-written and directed by François Alaux, Hervé de Crécy and Ludovic Houplain, the film is set in a stylized version of Los Angeles and portrays
various events as being told entirely through the extensive use of more than 2,000 contemporary and historical company logos and mascots.
The short's voice cast consists of Bob Stephenson, David Fincher, Aja Evans,
Sherman Augustus, Joel Michaely, Matt Winston, Gregory J.
Pruss, Josh Eichenbaum, Jaime Ray Newman and Andrew Kevin Walker.
Upon its premiere on 20 May 2009 in Cannes, Logorama has received numerous awards, including winning both the Kodak Discovery Award for Best Short Film (the
Kodak Prix) at the 2009 Cannes Film Festival and the Academy Award for Best Animated Short Film at the 82nd Academy Awards the following year.
The film explores themes of california, police, hostage, delinquent, zoo.
The tone is lighthearted.